Now, y'all know that that situation in Alabama, that was real.
That was crazy.
OK, that was a beautiful time.
And what it said to us was if we could collectively gather as black folks all the time, I feel like things would be very, very different.
I just think about the way in which so many of us were so empowered and excited by literally just us showing up that this brother didn't have to be by himself.
And how enthusiastic folks were to get on out there and get in the mix.
The brother was swimming.
The brothers came off the boat with the shirts off already.
And of course, we can never forget the folding chair of power.
OK, Moni over here was surprised I will remember that I will always remember August 5th and we should always remember August 5th.
It is a keep it.
And it's honestly interesting that earlier that day, there was a group of women who had come down to that very dock to do a spiritual ceremony atoning for the slaves that had been sold on that dock because it used to be an auction block.
And so earlier that day, they had come down there and said words and cleansed it and boom.